New York State Department of Labor Files 6152
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Alien Live-In Domestic Workers: A Study of Experience in the New York Metropolitan Area, 1967 and 1968 26 - 0082, 1967-1970 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Upstate Directory Towns and Cities Identified by Local Offices of Jurisdiction (Excepting Nassau, Suffolk, and Westchester Counties) 26 - 0083, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Department of Labor Division of Employment Program Plan Report Planning-Programming-Budgeting 1968 26 - 0084 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- State of New York Department of Labor Division of Employment Docs. Volume I- III 26 - 0085, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Claimants for Extended Benefits in New York State Under the Federal Temporary Unemployment Compensation Act of 1958 26 - 0086, 1958- 1959 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Notes for Papers and Speeches on New Concepts and Challenges in Manpower Utilization 26 - 0087, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Docs. Related to Vacation Unemployment Policy Pay Clarification and Benefit Claims 26 - 0088, 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- The Supervisor's Responsibility for Compliance with Laws, Regulations and Policies 26 - 0101, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Industrial Classification 26 - 0102, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Guide for Supervision of Counselor-Trainees 26 - 0103, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- How to Interview the Job Seeker ( A Study Item) 26 - 0104, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Orientation to Division of Employment July 1956 26 - 0105, 1956-1959 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Non-Discrimination - Claims Personnel August, 1960 26 - 0106 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Making Initial Determinations March 8, 1962 26 - 0107 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Maintenance and Use of Procedures Manuals October 1956 26 - 0108 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Introduction to the Placement Process 26 - 0109, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Labor Laws Affecting Placement of Minors May 1962 26 - 0110 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Summary of Experience Electronic Data Processing 26 - 0111, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- State of New York Department of Labor Division of Employment - Many Procedure Referendums 26 - 0112, 1953-1958 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- State of New York Department of Labor Division of Employment Planning Office Program + Policy Referendums 26 - 0112, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- New York State Department of Labor Division of Employment Planning Office Policy and Procedure Referendums 26 - 0112, 1960- 1962 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Division Reorganization 26 - 0113, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- New York State Division of Employment Employee Handbook You and Your Job 26 - 0114, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Financing Unemployment Insurance Benefits in New York State A Comparison of the Present Law and the Employers Conference Draft Bill of June 6, 1961 26 - 0115 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Estimated Status of New York Unemployment Insurance Fund 1958-1960 26 - 0116 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- The Pattern of Farm Employment in New York State Implications for Unemployment Insurance Coverage 26 - 0117, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- A Study of the Tax Base Under the New York State Unemployment Insurance Law 26 - 0118, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Impact of a Tax Base Increase 26 - 0119 (Box 16, Folder 45)
- State of New York - Department of Labor Division of Employment The Farm Placement Service 26 - 0120, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 46)
- Unemployment Insurance Disqualifications 26 - 0121, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 47)
- Control of Unemployment Insurance Claims on the New York Waterfront 26 - 0122, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 48)
- Employment in Agricultural Establishments Covered by Unemployment Insurance New York State 26 - 0123, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 49)
- Various Graphs Mostly Weekly Unemployment Insurance Claims 26 - 0124, 1942-1955 (Box 16, Folder 50)
- Variations in Employment, Payrolls, and Establishments Covered by Unemployment Insurance 26 - 0125, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 51)
- Unemployment Benefits and Family Finances 26 - 0126, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 52)
- TEC Claimants in Four Survey Periods New York State, 1961-1962 26 - 0127, 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 53)
- Teenagers and Young Adults - Their Work Experience 26 - 0128, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 54)
- T.U.C.* - The People It Helped 26 - 0129, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 55)
- The Older Population of New York State, 1957 26 - 0130, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 56)
- "Repeater" Negative Account Firms 26 - 0131, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Manpower Requirements in Electronics Manufacturing Outlook to 1964 in the New York Metropolitan Area 26 - 0132, 1960-1964 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- The Long Term Unemployed 1961-1962 26 - 0133, 1961-1964 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Docs. Related to Department of Labor Unemployment Insurance Appeal Board 26 - 0134, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- The Manpower Picture in New York City as of November 1966 26 - 0135, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Completion and Employment Experience of MDTA Enrollees in New York State 1963-1965 26 - 0136 (26-0073), 1935-1966 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Action Research Project Relating to the Long-Term Unemployed 26 - 0137, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Preliminary Report The Economy of Northern New York State 26 - 0138, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- State of New York - Department of Labor Division of Employment The Farm Placement Service 26 - 0139, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Jobless Secretaries and Stenographs in a Sellers' Market New York City, April 1953 26 - 0140 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Study of Interstate Claims from Puerto Rico 26 - 0141, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Report on Financing Unemployment Insurance in New York State Appendix Statistical Tables 26 - 0142, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Classified Labor Market Areas of New York State 26 - 0143, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Statement on the Use of Domestic and Foreign Labor in New York State 26 - 0144, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- State of New York Department of Labor Division of Employment the Hotel Placement Office 26 - 0145, 1951-1952 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Industry and Occupational Coverage of Prevailing Wage Surveys 26 - 0146, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- New York State Department of Labor Division of Employment Computation Procedure 26 - 0147, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Materials Prepared for the New York State Commission on Management and Productivity 27 - 0001, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Survey of the Employer Relations Office (ERO), Manpower Services Division, New York City 27 - 0002, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- I. Achieving MP Goals The More Effective Ex. Services Programs and II. Guidelines for Installing + Maintaining an Effective Employer Services Program Locally 27 - 0003, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Inter-Office Memorandum Placement Penetration Study in Onondaga County (Syracuse) January 1, 1976-June 30, 1976 27 - 0004 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Summary of Provisions of Unemployment Compensation Amendments of 1976, P.L. 94-566 (HR 10210) 27 - 0005 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Crime Does Not Pay Why New York State Employers Should be Concerned About Unemployment Insurance Fraud 27 - 0006, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Position Paper Utilization of Federal Social Security Wage Tapes for Cross Matching with Unemployment Insurance Benefits 27 - 0007, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Management Analysis and Improvement Office Quality Control Section Survey of the Local Office Reception Activity and its Effect on Referral and Placement Service 27 - 0008, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Quality Control Section Placement Validation Study Local Office #096, Elmira 27-0009, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Report on Audit of Selected Key Items - Local Office 33, Little Falls 27 - 0010, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Report on Audit of Selected Key Items - Local Office 544, Jamaica 22 - 0011, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Targeted Jobs Tax Credit 28 - 0001, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- How to Prepare Yourself for Job Interviews 28 - 0002, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Turnover and Absenteeism Reference Material 28 - 0003 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Equal Employment Opportunity in Apprenticeship Training Regulations 28 - 0004, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Apprenticeship Training (Article 23 of the New York State Labor Law) 28 - 0005, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Occupational Analysis - Industrial Services Section Recruiting Agreements with Correctional Services and State Police 28-0006, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Results of Wage and Salary Survey Job Service Employer Committee Westchester Chapters 28 - 0007, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- New York State Department of Labor Job Service Division Employer Information 28 - 0008, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Listing - Federal Contractors and Subcontractors 28 - 0009, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- A Review of the Dress Industry Placement Unit and Recommendations for Improved Service 29 - 0001, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- A Brief Resume of the New York State Employment Service 29 - 0002, 1896-1929 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  Docs. Do not appear to be from 1800s
- Tentative Administrative Districting of New York State for the Division of Unemployment Insurance 29 - 0003, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- A Study of the Programs of the New York State Employment Service 29 - 0004, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Facts About the New York State Employment Service 29 - 0005, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Report on Operation of the Experimental Bronx Day Work Offices 29 - 0006, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Employment Problems of Older Workers in New York City Part I. Findings and Conclusions 29 - 0007, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Employment Problems of Older Workers in New York City Part II. Statistical Supplement Part III. Follow - Up Questionnaire 29 - 0007 Pt.2, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- The Employment Situation in Service Industries Dependent on Water Transportation in the Port of New York 29 - 0008, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Report of the Committee on Household Employment 29 - 0009, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Unemployment Insurance in New York State 29 - 0010, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- A Survey of Shoe Manufacturing in New York City 29 - 0011, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Survey of Shoe Industry in Brooklyn 29 - 0012, 1918 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Enrolment for Farm Cadet Victory Service 29 - 0013 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Two Proposals for New ES Directions 29 - 0014, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Docs. Related to Cooperation between the New York State Employment Service, the National Reemployment Service and the Temporary Emergency Relief Administration 29 - 0015, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Survey of the Women's Neckwear Industry in New York City 29 - 0016, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Public Employment Service - New York State Report to Local Reemployment Committees 29 - 0017, 1933-1934 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- New York State Organization of National Reemployment Service. U.S. Department of Labor. 29 - 0018 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- ERB Industrial Survey 29 - 0019, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Reorganization of New York City Local Insurance Offices 29 - 0020, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Information Summary of Provisions of the Order for Minimum Wages in the Confectionery Industry 29 - 0021, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Report on the Experimental Project in the Placement of Puerto Rican Workers in Household Employment in Scarsdale, New York 29 - 0022, 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Why Young People Fail to Get and Hold Jobs 29 - 0023, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Junior Employment Work on Wheels by Evelyn Murray 29 - 0024, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Activities of Junior Sections New York State Employment Service 29 - 0025, 1938-1939 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Survey of Public Employment Service in New York City Volume I 29 - 0026, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Survey of Public Employment Service in New York City 29-0027, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Section D4-d-1 New York State Employment Service - Service to Juniors in New York City 29 - 0028, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Section D4-d-II Service for the Handicapped in the New York State Employment Service in New York City 29 - 0029, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Section D4-d-III New York State Employment Service - Service to Veterans in New York City 29 - 0030, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- Sections D4-d-IV New York State Employment Service Relationships with Other Public Agencies in New York City 29-0031, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Section D4-d-V New York State Employment Service Clearance of Labor in New York City 29 - 0032, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Section D4-d-VI New York State Employment Service Relationships with Unions in New York City 29 - 0033, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Section D4-d-VII Organization and Operation of the Central Professional Office of the New York State Employment Service in New York City 29 - 0034, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 35)
- Section D4-d-VIII Employer Visiting Program of the New York State Employment Service in New York City 29 - 0035, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- Section D4-d-IX Public Relations Program of the New York State Employment Service in New York City 29 - 0036, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Section D4-d-X New York State Employment Service Operation of Central Merchandise Unit in New York City 29 - 0037, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Section D4-d-Xa New York State Employment Service Operation of the Central Summer Resort Unit in New York City 29 - 0038, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Section D4-d-XI Placement Service to Household Employers Provided by the New York State Employment Service in New York City 29 - 0039, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Section D4-d-XII New York State Employment Service Operation of Letter Shop Unit in New York City 29 - 0040, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Section D4-d-XIII New York State Employment Service Staff Training in New York City, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Section D4-d-XIV Service to the Dress Industry Furnished by the New York State Employment Service in New York City 29 - 0042, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Section D4-d-XV Organization and Administration of the New York State Employment Service in New York City 29 - 0043, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Vol. I. General Administration Local Employment Office Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance 29 - 0044, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Industrial Bulletin v. 1 to v. 14 and Bulletin 1915-1920. (Box 28)
- Industrial Bulletin v. 31 to v. 46. (Box 29)
- Collective Bargaining Settlements and Work Stoppages. (Box 30)
- Unemployment Insurance Law. (Box 31)
- Industrial Bulletin v. 47 to v. 50 and Workers Compensation Board Bulletin. (Box 32)
- Collective Bargaining Settlements v. 12 to v. 26. (Box 33)
- State Labor Relations Board Annual Reports; Analysis of Decisions; Farm Labor; Adjudication Series. (Box 34)
- Joint and Legislative Committee on Unemployment Insurance. (Box 35)
- Special Labor Force Memorandum and Special Labor News Memorandum. (Box 36)
- Collective Bargaining Settlements v. 1 to v. 11. (Box 37)
- Reports and Minutes of the NYS Advisory Council. (Box 38)
- Division Annual Reports. (Box 39)
- Industrial Bulletin v. 15 to v. 30. (Box 40)
- Weekly Legislative Digest v. 1 to v. 16. (Box 41)
- Annual Reports of the Unemployment Insurance Appeal Board; Workers Compensation Board; Advisory Council. (Box 42)
- Key Facts and Figures. (Box 43)
- Work Stoppages in NYS. (Box 44)
- Division of Industrial Hygiene Studies, Bulletin and Annual Report of the Division of Hazard Abatement Board. (Box 45)
- Legislative Digest v. 17 to v. 32. (Box 46)
- Unemployment Insurance Tax Rates. (Box 47)
- Miscellaneous Research and Statistics and Division of Education Publications (mostly duplicates). (Box 48)
- Unemployment Insurance Benefits. (Box 49)
- Occupational Wage Bulletins; Unemployment Insurance Industry Reports; and Digest of Decisions. (Box 50)
- Benjamin Report and Miscellaneous Communication Reports and Collective Bargaining Settlements Annual Reports. (Box 51)
- Special Bulletins and Annual Reports Operations. (Box 52)
- Reports and Minutes of the NYS Advisory Council. (Box 53)
- Economic and Legal Briefs and Miscellaneous Documents. (Box 54)
- Rochester Employment Center and Miscellaneous Documents. (Box 55)
- Research Bulletins 1969 to 1972; Working Papers 1963 to 1966. (Box 56)
- Employment Statistics and Annual Evaluation of Unemployment Insurance Fund. (Box 57)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 58)
- Arbitration Proceedings Rochester Transit and Bell Aircraft. (Box 59)
- Reports to the Minimum Wage Boards. (Box 60)
- Reports to the Minimum Wage Boards. (Box 61)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 62)
- Training. (Box 63)
- Unemployment Insurance Industry Reports and Miscellaneous. (Box 64)
- Placement- Unemployment Insurance Bulletins, Active File Inventory, The Recorder. (Box 65)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 66)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 67)
- Unemployment Insurance. (Box 68)
- B Publications (Research and Statistics) 021-2095 to 21-2069. (Box 69)
- Labor Law. (Box 70)
- Unemployment Insurance and Workers Compensation Law. (Box 71)
- Unemployment Insurance and Workers Compensation Law. (Box 72)
- Labor Law. (Box 73)
- Labor Law. (Box 74)
- Working Women in New York State Reports 1936 to 1947. (Box 85)